Now we have created a complete classifier that takes in
现在 我们已经创建了一个完整的分类器
an RGB image and outputs a predicted label for any image.
它可以读了一个 RGB 图像 并输出任何图像的预测标签
The next step is to look at the accuracy of our model.
接下来 我们要看看模型的准确度
The accuracy of any classification model is found by comparing predicted and true labels.
分类模型的准确度可以通过预测标签和真实标签的对比确定
If the predicted label matches the true label,
如果预测标签和真实标签相吻合
then this is a correctly classified image.
就表示图像分类正确
If not, it is misclassified.
否则 就表示分类错误
The accuracy is given by the number of
准确度是指分类正确的图像
correctly classified images over the total number of images.
占图像总数的比例
And since we are using a pretty simple brightness feature here,
因为我们这里使用的亮度特征非常简单
we may not expect this classifier to be 100 percent accurate.
我们预期这个分类器不会 100% 准确
We will also be testing our classifier on new images.
我们还会在新图像上测试分类器
This is called a test set of data,
我们将其称作数据测试集
and test data is previously unseen image data.
测试数据是之前没见过的图像数据
The data you have seen and that you use to
之前见过、用来构建分类器的数据
help build a classifier is called training data.
叫做训练数据
In training data, are images like these.
在训练数据中 是这些图像
The idea in creating these two sets training and test is to have one set that
之所以要创建这两个集 训练集和测试集
you can analyze and learn from and one that you can actually test your classifier on.
是需要一个集进行学习 另一个集用于测试分类器
You could imagine creating a classifier that can
假设我们创建了一个分类器
classify all of these training images correctly,
可以正确对所有训练图像分类
but you actually want to build a classifier that recognizes general patterns and
但你实际上想构建一个分类器 能识别通用图案
data so that when it is faced with a real world scenario, it will still work.
和数据 保证分类器在面临真实长颈是也能正常工作
And so, we will load in a new test set of data to
因此 我们会载入一个新的数据测试集
see how a classification model might work in the real world,
看看分类模型在真实世界中的表现
and we'll use this to determine the accuracy of the model.
从而确定模型的准确度
We load in the test images and standardize them,
我们载入测试图像 对其归一化处理
and we finally shuffle them so that the order will not play a role in testing accuracy.
然后打乱重置 保证顺序对测试准确度不起作用
So, to determine the accuracy,
要确定准确度
I am going to iterate through this test data,
我需要遍历这个测试数据
and I am going to do this with a function called,
我需要使用一个函数
get_misclassified_images, and I will pass in my test images.
get_misclassified_images 代入我的测试图像
I will start with an empty list misclassified images and labels,
刚开始时 我使用一个空列表 misclassified_images_labels
and I'll iterate through each image in our test images.
然后遍历测试图像集中的每幅图像
I'll extract the true data,
提取真实数据
the image and its true label,
图像和真实标签
and I will run a classifier code to get
然后 运行分类器代码 使用估算标签函数并代入图像
a predicted label using our estimate label function and passing in the image.
得到预测标签
So for any image, we are using
因此 对于任何图像 我们都使用
our classification code to produce a predicted label for that image.
分类代码产生一个该图像的预测标签
Then, I'll compare the predicted label and the true label.
然后 我会对比预测标签和真实标签
If these matched, this image is classified correctly.
如果两者吻合 则图像分类正确
But if they do not match,
否则
this image has been misclassified,
图像分类错误
and I'll add the misclassified Images that predicted the end
接下来 我会把分类错误的图像、它们的预测值
their true labels to a list called, misclassified_images_labels.
和真实数值添加到一个列表 misclassified_images_labels
So again, I'm appending the image,
再次附加图像
its predicted label, and its true label.
其预测标签和真实标签
Finally, our trim this list of all our misclassified images and their labels.
最后 返回所有错误分类的图像及其标签的列表
Next, I'll do my accuracy calculations.
然后 我来计算准确度
First, I'll run this function, get_misclassified_images,
首先 在归一化的图像测试列表中
on our standardized test list of images,
运行这个函数 get_misclassified_images
and I'll store all them as classified images and labels in a list, Misclassified.
这些图像全部保存为一个分类图像和标签列表 Misclassified
Then I am going to store the total number of images
然后 存储图像总数量
by getting the length of our standardized test list.
只需获得归一化测试列表的长度即可
The number of correctly classified images will be
正确分类的图像等于
this total number minus the number of misclassified Images.
总数量减去错误分类的图像数量
Finally, we can calculate the accuracy, which as you recall,
最后 计算准确度 你可能记得
is our number of correctly classified images over our total number of images,
等于正确分类图像占图像总数的比例
then I am going to print these stats app.
然后 我把这些统计数字打印出来
And if we run this, we get .925 or 92.5 percent accuracy.
运行后 我们得的准确度为 0.925 或 92.5%
That is actually not bad.
还不算差
But with more features, I bet you could improve this algorithm.
如果特征更多 你肯定可以进一步完善这个算法
And to see how to improve,
要看看如何完善
it is useful to take a look at
我们可以观察
the misclassified Images and what they were mistakenly labeled as,
分类错误的图像 了解错误标签内容
and it will be up to you to look at these images and
你的任务是查看这些图像
think about how to improve the classification model.
并考虑如何完善分类模型